<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China Sees a Chance to Lure Jaded U.S. Allies</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china-sees-a-chance-to-lure-jaded-u-s-allies-3bc6ac6b</link>
      <description>Beijing has seized upon the disarray within the trans-Atlantic alliance and is trying to entice U.S. allies with the promise of reliable trade partnerships.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chinese Spy Machine Infiltrating Taiwan’s Military</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/taiwan-military-china-spy-network-a56ec8da</link>
      <description>Beijing’s rapidly advancing spying operations have seen agents penetrate the island’s armed forces, enticing personnel to pledge allegiance to China.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Imports to Help Lower U.K. Inflation to Target, BOE’s Taylor Says</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-imports-to-help-lower-u-k-inflation-to-target-boes-taylor-says-7c8efbb9</link>
      <description>The annual rate of inflation is likely to fall to the Bank of England’s 2% target by the middle of this year, aided by cheap imports from China, the rate-setter said.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Pushes Out Key Officials Focused on China Tech Threat</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/national-security/trump-administration-pushes-out-key-officials-focused-on-china-tech-threat-cd2dde3f</link>
      <description>The departing staffers worked for a Commerce Department office charged with protecting the U.S. from Chinese technological advances.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Signals Tolerance for Stronger Yuan</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/currencies/chinas-central-bank-sets-strongest-yuan-fixing-in-almost-three-years-e9196ff9</link>
      <description>The People’s Bank of China set the strongest reference rate for the currency in almost three years.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vanke Wins Reprieve on Overdue Bond Payments</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/business/china-vanke-wins-reprieve-on-overdue-bond-payments-388e8917</link>
      <description>The developer’s bondholders had previously rejected proposals to restructure payment on the bond.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Reports Robust Economic Growth, Thanks to Resilient Exports</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/china-reports-robust-economic-growth-thanks-to-resilient-exports-5b2ae07c</link>
      <description>Momentum slowed recently, with last year’s economic performance underscoring how China’s growth has become increasingly lopsided.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa Risks Angering Trump by Hosting Navies of Iran, Russia, China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/africa/south-africa-risks-angering-trump-by-hosting-navies-of-iran-russia-china-f55067a4</link>
      <description>The military exercises come at a time of already strained relations with the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Is on a Himalayan Building Spree to Prepare for a Clash With China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/india-is-on-a-himalayan-building-spree-to-prepare-for-a-clash-with-china-c914dcaf</link>
      <description>A deadly standoff jolted India to stitch together a huge network of roads, tunnels and landing strips needed to move soldiers and supplies to the mountainous border region.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi’s Enforcers Punished Nearly a Million in 2025—and China’s Leader Wants More</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/xis-enforcers-punished-nearly-a-million-in-2025and-chinas-leader-wants-more-019e1c65</link>
      <description>Xi Jinping has ordered the Communist Party’s discipline inspectors to flex their powers even more forcefully and ensure his policies are executed as intended.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>