<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China and Canada Edge Closer With Progress on Trade</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-and-canada-edge-closer-with-progress-on-trade-63ef2240</link>
      <description>Prime Minister Mark Carney’s visit to Beijing yields agreement on a “strategic partnership,” as China seeks to court countries grappling with volatile U.S. trade policies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Leader Spurned by Trump Finds a Warm Embrace in China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/canadian-leader-spurned-by-trump-finds-a-warm-embrace-in-china-a44ea147</link>
      <description>Beijing is hosting Mark Carney as it works to sustain its exports and woo U.S. allies frustrated with American protectionism.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 07:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese AI Developers Say They Can’t Beat America Without Better Chips</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/china-ai-race-us-chips-9e74b957</link>
      <description>Companies in China are jostling for access to Nvidia’s latest Rubin lineup while better-funded U.S. competitors are first in line.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Propaganda Playbook for Targeting Rivals</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-japan-taiwan-strategy-tactics-ab881734</link>
      <description>China’s state propaganda machine has a toolbox for undermining leaders that includes fake opinion polls, “lawfare” and general character assassination.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Record Trade Surplus Defies Expectations for Tariff-Driven Slowdown</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/china-marks-record-1-2-trillion-trade-surplus-in-2025-despite-u-s-tariffs-2dddf4e3</link>
      <description>The 2025 record showed that the world’s second-largest economy remained resilient despite facing steep Trump administration tariffs that slashed its exports to the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Imports to Help Lower U.K. Inflation to Target, BOE’s Taylor Says</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-imports-to-help-lower-u-k-inflation-to-target-boes-taylor-says-7c8efbb9</link>
      <description>The annual rate of inflation is likely to fall to the Bank of England’s 2% target by the middle of this year, aided by cheap imports from China, the rate-setter said.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Where’s Congress on Russia Sanctions?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/russia-sanctions-bill-donald-trump-iran-venezuela-china-north-korea-766038e1</link>
      <description>Trump has given the green light for a tariff bill on countries that buy Russian oil.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 22:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Blows Up China’s Latin America Ambitions With Maduro Ouster</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/china-trump-venezuela-maduro-75e95551</link>
      <description>Beijing is recalculating its policy of making inroads in Washington’s backyard after its top ally there was deposed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada Anticipates Progress in China Talks to Resolve Trade Row</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/canada-anticipates-progress-in-china-talks-to-resolve-trade-row-56d89a70</link>
      <description>Canada anticipates progress with China on resolving trade irritants regarding canola and electric vehicles during Prime Minister Mark Carney visit’s to Beijing this week, officials said.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Warns AI Startups Seeking to Emulate Meta Deal: Not So Fast</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/china-warns-ai-startups-seeking-to-emulate-meta-deal-not-so-fast-17bdd28a</link>
      <description>Beijing worries the $2.5 billion acquisition of startup Manus will encourage more entrepreneurs to follow in its footsteps.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Detains Church Leaders as Crackdown on Religion Intensifies</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-detains-church-leaders-as-crackdown-on-religion-intensifies-98f40ce2</link>
      <description>Authorities have taken away at least four members of a high-profile “house church” in Sichuan province as a campaign to root out religious organizations beyond the state’s control intensifies.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa Risks Angering Trump by Hosting Navies of Iran, Russia, China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/africa/south-africa-risks-angering-trump-by-hosting-navies-of-iran-russia-china-f55067a4</link>
      <description>The military exercises come at a time of already strained relations with the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Is on a Himalayan Building Spree to Prepare for a Clash With China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/india-is-on-a-himalayan-building-spree-to-prepare-for-a-clash-with-china-c914dcaf</link>
      <description>A deadly standoff jolted India to stitch together a huge network of roads, tunnels and landing strips needed to move soldiers and supplies to the mountainous border region.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S.’s Two Foremost Asian Allies Are on Good Terms—an Irritant for China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/the-u-s-s-two-foremost-asian-allies-are-on-good-termsan-irritant-for-china-71c7854e</link>
      <description>South Korean President Lee Jae Myung and Japanese Prime Minister Sanae Takaichi displayed unity in a high-profile summit.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Battle Over Who Runs the Panama Canal Ports Is About to Be Decided</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/business/logistics/panama-canal-port-china-ck-hutchinson-9b0c5a6b</link>
      <description>The Panamanian Supreme Court is winding up deliberations in a lawsuit that could void a Chinese company’s license to operate the ports and hand President Trump a win.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Isolated Iran Finds China’s Friendship Has Limits</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/an-isolated-iran-finds-chinas-friendship-has-limits-be947372</link>
      <description>Beijing denounced Trump’s 25% tariff on countries that do business with Tehran, but seems reluctant to offer more support.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>