<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Economy Is Deteriorating on Several Fronts</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/chinas-economy-is-deteriorating-on-several-fronts-6d0a4a9b</link>
      <description>The broad-based weakening spans consumer spending, investment and real estate.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 03:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Germany Wants a Divorce With China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/europe/why-germany-wants-a-divorce-with-china-0d59fb81</link>
      <description>For the first time in decades, German businesses and politicians are questioning the unfettered free trade that turned the country into an industrial powerhouse.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vanke Shares Fall After Bondholders Reject Debt Extension Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/business/china-vanke-shares-fall-after-bondholders-reject-debt-extension-proposal-bfab9d91</link>
      <description>The property developer said it will hold a bondholder meeting on Thursday to discuss next steps.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 05:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Court Convicts Publisher Jimmy Lai, Whom Trump Has Vowed to Free</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/hong-kong-court-convicts-publisher-jimmy-lai-whom-trump-has-vowed-to-free-8795674e</link>
      <description>The 78-year-old symbol of China’s protest crackdown faces a possible life sentence.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 03:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s OK of AI Chip Sales in China Called ‘Dangerous’ by Senate Democrats</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/national-security/trumps-ok-of-ai-chip-sales-in-china-called-dangerous-by-senate-democrats-ba0f84e9</link>
      <description>Sens. Elizabeth Warren, Chuck Schumer and other lawmakers said allowing sales of Nvidia’s H200 processors in China undoes past U.S. containment efforts</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Holding Chinese Man Who Documented Uyghur Camps</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/ice-holding-chinese-man-who-documented-uyghur-camps-a4702045</link>
      <description>Heng Guan is awaiting an immigration hearing on Monday that could lead to his removal from the U.S. and ultimately land him back in China, according to his lawyer and a New York-based activist group.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Forces Raid Ship, Seize Cargo Headed to Iran From China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/middle-east/u-s-forces-raid-ship-seize-cargo-headed-to-iran-from-china-35a1e2ac</link>
      <description>A U.S. special operations team boarded a ship in the Indian Ocean last month and seized military-related articles headed to Iran from China, U.S. officials said, an operation aimed at blocking Tehran from rebuilding its military arsenal.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>