<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Jets Locked Radar on Japanese Fighters</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-jets-locked-radar-on-japanese-fighters-16576128</link>
      <description>Tokyo said the incidents in international waters near Okinawa were dangerous, as diplomatic tensions with Beijing simmer.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 07:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How a Chinese Invasion of Taiwan Could Unfold</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/how-china-chinese-invasion-taiwan-ba7e3916</link>
      <description>An amphibious invasion would be one of the toughest military operations to pull off. This analysis shows why.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Authorities Summon Foreign Media to Criticize Fire Coverage</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/hong-kong-national-security-authorities-summon-foreign-media-over-fire-coverage-e8d4052b</link>
      <description>Hong Kong’s national-security office summoned representatives of news organizations including The Wall Street Journal to find fault with coverage of the deadly fire at Wang Fuk Court and warn against reporting that would undermine Hong Kong or its authorities.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 18:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Forces Battle Dizzying Altitudes to Expand Military Footprint</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-forces-battle-dizzying-altitudes-to-expand-military-footprint-c9350bbd</link>
      <description>A Wall Street Journal analysis of more than 100 satellite images shows clear evidence of the country’s expanding air power and reach.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Rare-Earth Dealers Find Ways to Dodge Beijing’s Export Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-rare-earth-dealers-find-ways-to-dodge-beijings-export-restrictions-0a96002a</link>
      <description>Companies are tweaking magnet formulas and embedding them in motors to keep selling to the West.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong’s Response to Deadly Fire Is Squeezed by China’s Firm Hand</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/hong-kongs-response-to-deadly-fire-is-squeezed-by-chinas-firm-hand-ea01b5a2</link>
      <description>Official efforts to control the public response include a threat to arrest those who direct their anger at the government.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Jimmy Lai’s Birthday Gift—to China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/jimmy-lais-birthday-giftto-china-9d7d4537</link>
      <description>Donald Trump’s visit to Beijing is an opening for the publisher’s release from prison.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Exports Rebound in November</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/chinas-exports-rebound-in-november-97f24e06</link>
      <description>Exports rose more than expected in November, bouncing from October’s dip and continuing to drive growth for the world’s second-largest economy.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Growth Is Coming at the Rest of the World’s Expense</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/chinas-growth-is-coming-at-the-rest-of-the-worlds-expense-99420396</link>
      <description>China is swallowing up a growing share of the world’s market for manufactured goods, revealing an uncomfortable truth: Beijing is pursuing a “beggar thy neighbor” growth model at everyone else’s expense.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s National-Security Strategy Softens Language on China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/trumps-national-security-strategy-softens-language-on-china-f121ddb3</link>
      <description>The White House document maintains some tough talk on Taiwan but drops references to Beijing as America’s main challenger.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Services-Sector Activity Growth Slows</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/central-banking/chinas-services-sector-activity-growth-slows-09b1f424</link>
      <description>The RatingDog general services purchasing managers index fell to 52.1, marking the lowest level in five months, according to a statement released Wednesday.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 02:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Newly Confident China Is Jockeying for More Global Clout as Trump Pulls Back</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/a-newly-confident-china-is-jockeying-for-more-global-clout-as-trump-pulls-back-5cc3be4e</link>
      <description>Feeling empowered after a clash over trade, Beijing is looking to exploit America’s inward turn.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>