<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China Is Too Big to Rely on Exports for Growth, IMF Chief Warns</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-is-too-big-to-rely-on-exports-for-growth-imf-chief-warns-c1a8654d</link>
      <description>On a visit to Beijing, the economist urged the government to get people spending more.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia AI Chips to Undergo Unusual U.S. Security Review Before Export to China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/nvidia-ai-chips-to-undergo-unusual-u-s-security-review-before-export-to-china-5e73cd55</link>
      <description>Shipping chips from Taiwan to the U.S. to China would allow government to get 25% cut of sales.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump’s U-Turn on Nvidia Chips Changes the Game for China’s AI</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/china-ai-nvidia-trump-chip-export-ban-lift-c3d457c1</link>
      <description>President Trump’s deal instantly reshaped the U.S.-China technological Cold War. The fear among his critics is he just helped Beijing catch up.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says U.S. Will Allow Nvidia H200 Chip Sales to China, Get 25% Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/nvidia-china-exports-h2000-chips-5943aa48</link>
      <description>The president’s decision to allow exports of the powerful chip comes after meeting last week with the company’s CEO, Jensen Huang.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Trump Says Chips Ahoy to Xi Jinping</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/nvidia-chips-donald-trump-china-xi-jinping-artificial-intelligence-3c55080f</link>
      <description>Why is he giving an adversary access to advanced AI semiconductors—and for what in return?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Manufacturing Is Booming Despite Trump’s Tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinas-manufacturing-is-booming-despite-trumps-tariffs-911fbcbe</link>
      <description>U.S. pressure has only cemented its rival’s status as the world’s indispensable factory floor, sending its trade surplus above $1 trillion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Trade Surplus Tops $1 Trillion, Underscoring Its Export Dominance</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/chinas-exports-rebound-in-november-97f24e06</link>
      <description>The historic milestone comes as China adds high-end manufacturing strength to its established dominance in lower-end goods.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 10:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Jets Locked Radar on Japanese Fighters</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-jets-locked-radar-on-japanese-fighters-16576128</link>
      <description>Tokyo said the incidents in international waters near Okinawa were dangerous, as diplomatic tensions with Beijing simmer.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 07:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How a Chinese Invasion of Taiwan Could Unfold</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/how-china-chinese-invasion-taiwan-ba7e3916</link>
      <description>An amphibious invasion would be one of the toughest military operations to pull off. This analysis shows why.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Authorities Summon Foreign Media to Criticize Fire Coverage</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/hong-kong-national-security-authorities-summon-foreign-media-over-fire-coverage-e8d4052b</link>
      <description>Hong Kong’s national-security office summoned representatives of news organizations including The Wall Street Journal to find fault with coverage of the deadly fire at Wang Fuk Court and warn against reporting that would undermine Hong Kong or its authorities.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 18:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s National-Security Strategy Softens Language on China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/trumps-national-security-strategy-softens-language-on-china-f121ddb3</link>
      <description>The White House document maintains some tough talk on Taiwan but drops references to Beijing as America’s main challenger.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Forces Battle Dizzying Altitudes to Expand Military Footprint</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-forces-battle-dizzying-altitudes-to-expand-military-footprint-c9350bbd</link>
      <description>A Wall Street Journal analysis of more than 100 satellite images shows clear evidence of the country’s expanding air power and reach.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>