<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China Detains Church Leaders as Crackdown on Religion Intensifies</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-detains-church-leaders-as-crackdown-on-religion-intensifies-98f40ce2</link>
      <description>Authorities have taken away at least four members of a high-profile “house church” in Sichuan province as a campaign to root out religious organizations beyond the state’s control intensifies.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cambodian Scam Tycoon Wanted by U.S. Extradited to China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/cambodian-scam-tycoon-wanted-by-u-s-extradited-to-china-b483e24c</link>
      <description>The Justice Department accused Chen Zhi of running a sprawling scam empire targeting Americans.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Forex Reserves Rose in December as Yuan Debate Mounts</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/finance/currencies/chinas-forex-reserves-rose-in-december-as-yuan-debate-mounts-d9636b7b</link>
      <description>China’s foreign-exchange reserves rose in December amid a weaker dollar, wrapping up a year marked by a ballooning trade surplus.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Ramps Up Dispute With Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/china-ramps-up-dispute-with-japan-d2a38bf1</link>
      <description>Beijing banned exports to Japan that could have military uses, escalating a feud over Taiwan.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why China Stopped Publicly Urging for North Korean Denuclearization</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/why-china-stopped-publicly-urging-for-north-korean-denuclearization-8872b47a</link>
      <description>Beijing has fewer reasons to alienate Pyongyang, turning down chances to openly back disarmament such as at a state visit by South Korea’s president.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada’s Carney to Visit China Next Week With Focus on Trade</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/canadas-carney-to-visit-china-next-week-with-focus-on-trade-37713a1c</link>
      <description>It’s Prime Minister Mark Carney’s latest step to normalize ties with the world’s second-largest economy and reduce Canada’s reliance on the U.S. for trade.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro’s Capture Threatens China’s Ambitions in Latin America</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/maduros-capture-threatens-chinas-ambitions-in-latin-america-09ada754</link>
      <description>Beijing has steadily built relationships over the past two decades in Washington’s backyard.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Signals It Won’t Give an Inch to the U.S. in Latin America</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/china-signals-it-wont-give-an-inch-to-the-u-s-in-latin-america-ba03bd24</link>
      <description>Beijing is doubling down on its expansion just as President Trump tries to claim the Western Hemisphere as an exclusive sphere of influence for the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Says China Hit 2025 Growth Target Despite Economic Headwinds</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/xi-says-china-hit-2025-growth-target-despite-economic-headwinds-dcedc9c8</link>
      <description>The leader’s New Year speech is an opportunity to communicate directly with the Chinese people and provided an insight into his priorities.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Takeaways From China’s Military Drills Around Taiwan</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/five-takeaways-from-chinas-military-drills-around-taiwan-47c64aee</link>
      <description>Beijing encircled the island this week and warned outsiders to stay away.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 10:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Factory Activity Gauges Signal Return to Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/chinas-factory-activity-expanded-in-december-bfe01eee</link>
      <description>China’s factory activity signaled a return to growth in December, according to both official and private surveys, an improvement likely to help Beijing achieve its growth target for the year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 02:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Is on a Himalayan Building Spree to Prepare for a Clash With China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/india-is-on-a-himalayan-building-spree-to-prepare-for-a-clash-with-china-c914dcaf</link>
      <description>A deadly standoff jolted India to stitch together a huge network of roads, tunnels and landing strips needed to move soldiers and supplies to the mountainous border region.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>