<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Sprint for Tech Dominance Can’t Hide an Economy Full of Holes</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-economy-gap-tech-advance-970296f1</link>
      <description>A self-sufficiency push has made China a tougher competitor to the U.S., but it comes with enormous waste.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to Impose Provisional Anti-Subsidy Duties on EU Dairy Products</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-to-impose-provisional-anti-subsidy-duties-on-eu-dairy-products-82c95ab2</link>
      <description>According to a preliminary ruling, most EU companies will face rates below 30%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14-Hour Shifts and $1 a Delivery—but China’s Army of Gig Workers Keeps Growing</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/14-hour-shifts-and-1-a-deliverybut-chinas-army-of-gig-workers-keeps-growing-81ce58e4</link>
      <description>In a country once known for its factory workforce, some 200 million people are turning to informal roles as job creation slows.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Approves $11 Billion in Arms Sales to Taiwan, Angering Beijing</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/u-s-approves-11-billion-in-arms-sales-to-taiwan-angering-beijing-e523a54b</link>
      <description>The packages include Himars truck-based missile launchers, howitzers, missiles and antitank drones.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | China Stalks a Hong Kong Dissident Abroad</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/carmen-lau-china-embassy-london-u-k-hong-kong-c170e10b</link>
      <description>First came a bounty. Next came false sexually explicit letters about the U.K. resident.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors Deadlock in Trial of Linda Sun, Accused of Acting as China Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/us-news/law/jurors-deadlock-in-trial-of-linda-sun-accused-of-acting-as-china-agent-8ed1f027</link>
      <description>A mistrial was declared on charges against the former New York state aide and her husband.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vanke’s Brewing Crisis Suggests Limited Property Easing to Come</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/housing/china-vankes-brewing-crisis-suggests-limited-property-easing-to-come-020fd388</link>
      <description>Many of China’s other large developers have already defaulted, and a Vanke collapse would raise questions about how policymakers plan to address the real-estate slump as it drags on into a sixth year in 2026.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 08:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China Built an Arms Industry to Rival the West</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/how-beijing-built-arms-industry-to-rival-the-west-2ef824c7</link>
      <description>Beijing’s ability to churn out advanced armaments is a key element in Xi Jinping’s vision of making his country less reliant on the outside world.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tackles Concerns Over Taiwan Strategy With Massive Weapons Deal</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/trump-tackles-concerns-over-taiwan-strategy-with-massive-weapons-deal-211d2528</link>
      <description>The $11.1 billion sale came after a string of episodes that stirred disquiet about the U.S. president’s appetite to face down China.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panama Ports Deal Hits Impasse as China Makes New Demands for Its Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/business/logistics/panama-ports-deal-hits-impasse-as-china-makes-new-demands-for-its-approval-ff741523</link>
      <description>Beijing threatened to block the BlackRock-led deal to buy ports unless state-owned Cosco gets a majority stake.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>