<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Rare-Earth Dealers Find Ways to Dodge Beijing’s Export Restrictions</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-rare-earth-dealers-find-ways-to-dodge-beijings-export-restrictions-0a96002a</link>
      <description>Companies are tweaking magnet formulas and embedding them in motors to keep selling to the West.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong’s Response to Deadly Fire Is Squeezed by China’s Firm Hand</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/hong-kongs-response-to-deadly-fire-is-squeezed-by-chinas-firm-hand-ea01b5a2</link>
      <description>Official efforts to control the public response include a threat to arrest those who direct their anger at the government.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Services-Sector Activity Growth Slows</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/central-banking/chinas-services-sector-activity-growth-slows-09b1f424</link>
      <description>The RatingDog general services purchasing managers index fell to 52.1, marking the lowest level in five months, according to a statement released Wednesday.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 02:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Newly Confident China Is Jockeying for More Global Clout as Trump Pulls Back</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/a-newly-confident-china-is-jockeying-for-more-global-clout-as-trump-pulls-back-5cc3be4e</link>
      <description>Feeling empowered after a clash over trade, Beijing is looking to exploit America’s inward turn.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Private Gauge Signals Weaker Manufacturing Activity</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/global/china-private-gauge-signals-weaker-manufacturing-activity-4d83c8b4</link>
      <description>Growth in China’s manufacturing production came to a halt as new orders nearly stalled last month despite a renewed rise in new orders from abroad.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Manufacturing Gauge Shows Slightly Firmer Growth Momentum</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-manufacturing-gauge-shows-slightly-firmer-growth-momentum-5b49c27a</link>
      <description>China’s official factory gauge edged up on stronger production and demand in November, but remained in contraction for an eighth straight month.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Used to Be a Cash Cow for Western Companies. Now It’s a Test Lab.</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/china-used-to-be-a-cash-cow-for-western-companies-now-its-a-test-lab-2c5e52e8</link>
      <description>Competition has pushed some brands to adapt to Chinese tastes and introduce lower prices—and use the country as an innovation hub.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will India and China Be Able to Resist U.S. Sanctions on Russian Oil?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/india-china-trump-russia-sanctions-e4ba5b59</link>
      <description>New Delhi and Beijing have so far resisted U.S. calls to stop buying Russian crude, but far-reaching sanctions will be hard to ignore.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Russia and China Are Sitting Out Venezuela’s Clash With Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/why-russia-and-china-are-sitting-out-venezuelas-clash-with-trump-0fcc7710</link>
      <description>The ‘Axis of Authoritarianism’ is depleted by the war in Ukraine and preoccupied with trade negotiations.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>