<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>U.K.’s Starmer Joins Ranks of U.S. Allies Testing China’s Embrace</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/u-k-s-starmer-joins-ranks-of-u-s-allies-testing-chinas-embrace-f266150c</link>
      <description>In a visit to Beijing, the British leader is seeking to rekindle ties with Xi Jinping, with a business delegation in tow.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Agrees to Lower Tariffs by Half on U.K. Whisky</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/china-agrees-to-lower-tariffs-by-half-on-u-k-whisky-9a68469d</link>
      <description>The U.K. government said it expects whisky exports to China to be worth roughly $345.2 million to the economy over the next five years as tariffs are lowered to 5% from 10%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Approves Purchases of Nvidia’s H200 Chip, Easing Tension With U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/china-approves-purchases-of-nvidias-h200-chip-easing-tension-with-u-s-daa1ec84</link>
      <description>Beijing gave the green light to Alibaba and others, but is keeping in place limits intended to encourage purchases of local chips.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 07:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stung by Trump, America’s Top Trading Partners Shift Gaze to China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/us-trade-partners-china-aa5c020b</link>
      <description>America’s postwar allies are weighing closer ties to Beijing as they scour the globe for alternative markets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Imports to Help Lower U.K. Inflation to Target, BOE’s Taylor Says</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-imports-to-help-lower-u-k-inflation-to-target-boes-taylor-says-7c8efbb9</link>
      <description>The annual rate of inflation is likely to fall to the Bank of England’s 2% target by the middle of this year, aided by cheap imports from China, the rate-setter said.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Guan Heng Gets U.S. Asylum</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/guan-heng-asylum-ruling-china-uyghurs-charles-ouslander-department-of-homeland-security-b70be0c8</link>
      <description>A judge grants refuge to a worthy dissident, no thanks to DHS.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Local Governments Cut Growth Targets</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/chinas-local-governments-cut-growth-targets-4eb9e702</link>
      <description>More than a dozen Chinese provinces have cut their growth targets for the year, stoking speculation that Beijing will follow suit and set a lower national goal for 2026.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Man Who Documented Uyghur Population Is Granted U.S. Asylum</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinese-man-who-documented-uyghur-population-is-granted-u-s-asylum-2d8dffe5</link>
      <description>The citizen-journalist, Heng Guan, drew attention after he was detained by U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Jinping Is Stripping Down His Military Command and Starting Over</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/xi-jinping-is-stripping-down-his-military-command-and-starting-over-2e747c07</link>
      <description>Since mid-2023, at least 60 senior military officers and defense-industry executives have been placed under investigation, removed from public office or abruptly replaced.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:34:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vanke Avoids Immediate Default With More Bond Repayment Deferrals</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/business/china-vanke-avoids-immediate-default-with-more-bond-repayment-deferrals-19667d27</link>
      <description>The Chinese developer also obtained a fresh loan from a state-owned shareholder, giving it more breathing room as it wrestles with a prolonged liquidity crunch.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Deflation Doom Loop Trapping China’s Economy</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/deflation-doom-loop-china-economy-25b0938a</link>
      <description>Exports drive growth while race-to-the-bottom competition from overproduction hits prices, profits, wages and sales.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa Risks Angering Trump by Hosting Navies of Iran, Russia, China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/africa/south-africa-risks-angering-trump-by-hosting-navies-of-iran-russia-china-f55067a4</link>
      <description>The military exercises come at a time of already strained relations with the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Is on a Himalayan Building Spree to Prepare for a Clash With China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/india-is-on-a-himalayan-building-spree-to-prepare-for-a-clash-with-china-c914dcaf</link>
      <description>A deadly standoff jolted India to stitch together a huge network of roads, tunnels and landing strips needed to move soldiers and supplies to the mountainous border region.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Buildup of Chinese Military Fuels Corruption Scandals</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/rapid-buildup-of-chinese-military-fuels-corruption-scandals-2ca8a132</link>
      <description>A purge of military elite shows the risk of a sudden surge in military spending—and of crossing Xi Jinping.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Top General Accused of Giving Nuclear Secrets to U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/chinas-top-general-accused-of-giving-nuclear-secrets-to-u-s-b8f59dae</link>
      <description>Bribery allegations have also been leveled against Gen. Zhang Youxia, whose downfall carries implications for the country’s military readiness.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Built a Vast Oil Stake in Venezuela. Now It Risks Getting Muscled Out.</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/china-venezuela-oil-trump-65ce1da2</link>
      <description>Beijing’s moves bought it sway in Venezuela—all of it now subject to the Trump administration’s preferences in the wake of Maduro’s ouster.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>