<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>China News Filter</title>
    <link>https://www.wsj.com/world</link>
    <description>Custom RSS feed for WSJ_China</description>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Forces Raid Ship, Seize Cargo Headed to Iran From China</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/middle-east/u-s-forces-raid-ship-seize-cargo-headed-to-iran-from-china-35a1e2ac</link>
      <description>A U.S. special operations team boarded a ship in the Indian Ocean last month and seized military-related articles headed to Iran from China, U.S. officials said, an operation aimed at blocking Tehran from rebuilding its military arsenal.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tibetan Activists Say China Has Detained Protesters Who Staged Rare Act of Defiance</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/asia/tibetan-activists-say-china-has-detained-protesters-who-staged-rare-act-of-defiance-408e9e8b</link>
      <description>Chinese authorities arrested dozens of Tibetans who were protesting a mining project, according to Tibetan activists and the government in exile.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Another $12 Billion for a Tariff Bailout</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/opinion/donald-trump-tariffs-bailout-trade-wars-soybeans-china-24d0696f</link>
      <description>Trump’s latest round of aid for U.S. farmers hurt by his global trade wars.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 22:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s OK of AI Chip Sales in China Called ‘Dangerous’ by Senate Democrats</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/politics/national-security/trumps-ok-of-ai-chip-sales-in-china-called-dangerous-by-senate-democrats-ba0f84e9</link>
      <description>Sens. Elizabeth Warren, Chuck Schumer and other lawmakers said allowing sales of Nvidia’s H200 processors in China undoes past U.S. containment efforts</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Holding Chinese Man Who Documented Uyghur Camps</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/ice-holding-chinese-man-who-documented-uyghur-camps-a4702045</link>
      <description>Heng Guan is awaiting an immigration hearing on Monday that could lead to his removal from the U.S. and ultimately land him back in China, according to his lawyer and a New York-based activist group.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Friends of an Alleged Chinese Agent Whose Fate Now Rests With a Jury</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/world/china/meet-the-friends-of-an-alleged-chinese-agent-whose-fate-now-rests-with-a-jury-fc7e0d22</link>
      <description>Linda Sun, a former New York state aide, was often pictured with some of the Chinese Communist Party’s allies in the U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to Implement Export Controls on Some Steel Products</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/china-to-implement-export-controls-on-some-steel-products-560f9927</link>
      <description>Officials said exporters would need permission to ship any of 300 specified steel products starting Jan. 1.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Slaps Up to 50% Tariffs on Chinese Goods, Drawing Outcry From Beijing</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/economy/trade/china-urges-mexico-to-drop-protectionist-practices-in-tariff-spat-0b606c35</link>
      <description>Lawmakers pass levies targeting countries that Mexico has no trade agreement with, including China.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>